AUGUST 1, 2018
11:35 P.M.
YEONJIDOL VILLAGE, MADVILLE TOWN
LUNACY DISTRICT, MANIAC PROVINCE
Seriously?
There's a psychiatric hospital
in a place like this?
It's supposed to be somewhere
near Yeonjidol Mountain,
- so it should be around... Hey!
- What?
Over there.
Oh, I see it.
Dang.
I think that's it.
Hey! What's that?
What is this?
What on earth?
Isn't that for a shamanic rite?
What's that doing here?
It's kind of creepy.
Hey, this doesn't feel right.
Let's just take a look.
Are you sure?
DO NOT ENTER
Hey, you open it.
Oh man.
Looks like it's been closed for ages.
Everything looks so worn down.
- What if it's really haunted?
- Don't say stuff like that.
Hey, what's that?
- What now? What is it?
- Look.
It's a ghost!
- That's really a ghost, no?
- Wait.
No, that's a real person!
There's been a murder.
This is Crime Scene.
One detective
and five suspects.
Everyone takes on a role and an alibi
in this role-playing deduction game.
The real culprit is the only suspect
who can lie.
To clear their names
and to find the real culprit,
everyone must become
both suspect and detective
at the same time.
The clues point to the truth
and unexpected twists.
Will they succeed in catching the culprit?
CRIME SCENE ZERO
WARNING
LANDSLIDE PRONE AREA
DO NOT ENTER
AUGUST 1, 2018
YEONJIDOL VILLAGE
YEONJIDOL AND BANJIDOL BECOME ONE AGAIN!
THE HERO OF YEONJIDOL, PARK VILLAGE HEAD!
Wow.
Man, the trip over here...
YEONJIDOL VILLAGE CODE OF CONDUCT
...was really rough.
Why did they build
such a big psychiatric hospital
in the middle of nowhere?
Gosh, it looks creepy.
Oh dear.
Wait.
What's that?
How did a body end up
on the power lines outside the building?
A BODY HANGING FROM THE POWER LINES
OUTSIDE AN ABANDONED HOSPITAL
MURDER IN THE ABANDONED HOSPITAL I
I saw the crime scene photos
before coming here,
but it's so much worse in person.
So this place used to be a hospital,
- but now it's totally shut down.
- Jang Detective.
Hello.
- Hey!
- I'm Kang Minhee, the assistant detective.
ASSISTANT DETECTIVE
KANG MINHEE
- The assistant detective.
- Yes.
The AD.
- Yes, the AD.
- Great to meet you.
Looks like our very first case together
is going to be a tough one.
- Are you up for the challenge?
- Of course.
- I have nerves of steel.
- I see.
- I'll take your word for it.
- Thank you.
Now, I need an overview of today's case.
- I've compiled everything for you.
- Okay.
CASE FILE DELIVERED
All right, then.
Let's start by interviewing
all the suspects.
- I'll bring everyone here.
- Okay. Thanks.
The victim is Jang Je-in,
a 46-year-old female.
She was the director
of Yeonjidol Psychiatric Hospital,
which opened in 2006.
She disappeared in 2013
when the hospital shut down
and was found dead this evening,
hanging by the hospital's exterior wall.
The cause of death is severe blood loss.
The estimated time of death
is between 10:20 p.m. and 11:30 p.m.
The report came in at 11:35 p.m.
- What the heck is that?
- What on earth happened?
What is that?
How could something like this
happen in our village?
What the heck?
- Je-in.
- How distasteful.
- Could this be...
- The gods have been angered.
- Je-in.
- Oh dear.
Who could've done such a terrible thing?
What a mess. I don't have time for this.
- What's the matter with this guy?
- Why is he...
Je-in.
WHAT IS HIS CONNECTION TO THE VICTIM?
- Do you know him?
- All right.
I know this must be
a lot to take in for all of you,
not to mention the shock.
But as you can see,
there's been a murder,
and the five of you here
- have been identified as suspects.
- The Goddess of Birth is furious.
Her spirit will never be at peace.
ONE OF THEM IS THE MURDERER
As you can see,
this scene of the murder
is quite grotesque.
- We can't help but wonder
- How did she get up there?
why the murder took place up there,
of all places.
Let's go over the details together.
Please come with me.
RELOCATING FOR QUESTIONING
Hey, AD! Bring that body down.
This way, please.
- Oh my, I'm in Park Village Head's room.
- Thank you for having us.
DIGGING INTO THE SUSPECTS
First suspect, Park Village Head.
A 60-year-old male.
The head of Yeonjidol Village.
Second suspect, Jang Cousin.
A 51-year-old male.
The victim's cousin
and owner of a mannequin factory.
Third suspect, Kim Handsome.
A 32-year-old male.
A medical sales rep.
Fourth suspect, An Doctor.
A 46-year-old female.
A house call physician.
Fifth suspect, Park Shaman.
A 46-year-old female.
The village shaman.
I was driving over here,
thinking it was some backwoods village,
but then I realized it was Yeonjidol.
- This place is known for honey, right?
- That's right.
All thanks to our Village Head.
- Of course.
- We owe it all to him.
I also saw those big banners
on the way here.
Is there some event happening?
Our village is expanding tomorrow
by officially merging
with Banjidol Village.
It's a doubly special day
because Park Village Head
will be announced
as the first head of the joint village.
He may be the first,
- but he'll likely serve for life.
- Oh, stop it.
What a suck-up.
Okay.
Why are you crying?
Now, then.
Let's start with you,
Mr. Park Village Head.
What's the nature of your relationship
with the victim, Jang Je-in?
Ms. Jang built the psychiatric hospital
and she was the director.
She should've taken responsibility
and seen things through,
but she disappeared five years ago.
- And now...
- It's been in ruins for a while.
- Outsiders think it's haunted,
- Right.
- so they've been coming to check it out.
- It's true that ghosts roam those halls.
Our Mr. Village Head has been
so stressed over that.
He's always working
incredibly hard for our village,
and that's why he's getting
those circles under his eyes.
Are you the deputy head, then?
Oh, no. Well, I'm the cousin of Je-in,
- the poor girl who's hanging up there.
- Is that so?
What do you do for a living?
Well, at the moment,
- I just run a small mannequin factory.
- A mannequin factory?
I see.
Next up... Oh boy.
That outfit's too much.
Let me come back to you.
- Sorry?
- An Doctor, is it?
Oh, well...
As you can tell by the name, I'm a doctor.
I mainly make house calls
for VIP patients.
- I've never seen her around.
- Me neither.
I'm guessing you're not from around here.
Yes, she's an outsider.
Wait, that thing on your wrist
doesn't look like your typical jewelry.
My wrist? Oh, this.
Do you mean this?
- Yes.
- She has a tattoo too?
Do you know what "savior" means?
Did you say "swiper"?
What is she on about?
You mean you swiped the bracelet?
"Savior" means someone who saves others.
That's what my patients call me.
They call me their savior.
Then what's the nature
of your relationship with the victim?
Why did you end up becoming a suspect?
I'm not entirely sure why I'm here either,
but we were colleagues
back when we worked in Seoul.
Oh, so you two worked
in the medical field together?
I see. Well noted.
My hunch says
there was long-standing resentment
from bullying or workplace harassment
that eventually turned
into a fatal grudge.
Okay, then.
Jeez, that outfit really is bothersome.
One wrong move and you'll get possessed.
I thought so too. I'm on my guard.
- Ms. Park Shaman?
- Yes.
I'm Park Shaman, serving the gods
and spirits as the shaman of this village.
Since you're here...
If you need anything resolved...
I thought it was a talisman,
not a business card.
Connections here in the mortal realm
are formed for a reason.
What was your relationship
with the victim?
We went to high school together.
- High school?
- You know,
this is a small village, so basically
everyone attended Yeonjidol High School.
I see.
To be honest, you're one of the people
I felt that didn't quite belong
in this village, Mr. Kim Handsome.
Could you introduce yourself?
Oh dear. He seems to be
beside himself with grief.
Are you really sad?
You're not laughing, are you?
I'm...
- I'm actually Je-in's boyfriend.
- What?
- Her boyfriend?
- Boyfriend?
- She sure got around.
I'm her cousin and even I had no idea.
We were in love with each other
for a very long time.
Now that I'm faced with
such an unexpected, horrible event,
I don't know what to do.
What do you do for a living?
Well, I'm a medical sales rep.
- Medical sales?
- I see.
Is that how you met the victim?
Through work?
- I guess, but not exactly.
- While you were selling your products?
What sort of medical equipment
would a psychiatric hospital have needed?
Not much, I'm guessing.
There's probably more to it than that.
The victim was 46 years old.
- If you don't mind, how old are you?
- I'm 32.
- What?
- You're 32?
- See what I mean?
- Why is everyone so shocked?
- Goodness.
- You're just a baby.
- He clearly had ulterior motives.
Arrest him now, Mr. Detective!
Age is nothing but a number
when it comes to love.
What matters is how the couple
feels about each other.
I don't trust outsiders.
No one who lives
in a small village like this
would be capable of anything like murder.
We're all gentle folks.
- Exactly.
- The killer must be one of the outsiders.
Of course,
Mr. Village Head is absolutely right!
That kind of unsavory business
would never happen in our village!
With that being said,
stagnant water tends to rot.
What the hell does that mean?
What's gotten into you, Mole-rye?
Come on, Cousin.
-"Mole-rye"?
- Who's Mole-rye?
- What's with the old-fashioned nickname?
- Who is that?
- Is that what she's called when possessed?
- We all grew up together, you know.
- It's just a nickname I gave her.
- Right.
- We were never that close.
- All right.
So is it true that Ms. Jang came back here
for the first time in five years?
- Why'd she suddenly come back?
- Five years sounds about right.
- Did you all know she was back?
- Did you know, Cousin?
I think I heard that she was coming back
or that she had come back to the village.
I knew such rumors
were flying around, that's all.
- Talks that someone had seen her.
- I heard she was back after five years
from one of my regular clients,
the manager of Yeonjidol Hotel.
I heard the day before
that she was staying there.
What about you, Mr. Kim Handsome?
- Did you stay with her?
- Were you perhaps...
He must have!
No, I hadn't seen her
for a long time either.
- What kind of boyfriend is that?
- We both missed each other desperately,
but life got in the way at every turn,
so it had been a while.
All right, so the time of death
is estimated to be
between 10:20 p.m. and 11:30 p.m.
Please tell me what you were doing
and where you were during that time.
Mr. Kim Handsome?
Doing some murdering, no doubt!
What are you talking about?
I was at the hotel.
I only got here around 11:40 p.m.,
which is when I first heard the news
and broke into pieces.
Why are you staring at me?
- You've been bothering me, Ms. An Doctor.
- Have I?
Stop trying to seduce me.
Move your leg over to that side.
This is not okay.
- Hang on, Mr. Kim Handsome.
- Please move your leg.
I should perform a rite for him.
That's like a disease, you know.
Okay, I feel a lot better now.
Do you know how uncomfortable I was?
- All right, just keep talking.
- Women. How typical.
I keep getting the feeling
he might've been a patient here.
- Okay, next is Ms. Park... Park Shaman.
- Park Shaman, yes.
Where would a servant of the gods be?
- I was praying at the shrine.
- All right.
What about you, Mr. Jang Cousin?
I was just at home,
having some soju with kimchi.
How come?
Why were you home
when we had the eve festival going on?
- I don't really like crowds, and--
- But you said you were my right-hand man.
How strange.
You said so yourself.
And you, Ms. An Doctor?
I was tending to a VIP patient.
- A regular patient, I'm guessing?
- Yes.
- What about you, Mr. Park Village Head?
- Today was the eve festival,
- and tomorrow's the inauguration.
- Of course.
There was a singing contest
and everything,
so I was very busy
running around everywhere.
I can't even recall what I did.
The four of you told me
the specific location you were in,
- but Mr. Village Head's the only one who...
- Yes, I have a clear alibi.
- Unclear, you mean.
- Not clear. Unclear.
If our Mr. Village Head says it's clear,
it's clear!
"Running around everywhere"
doesn't sound so clear.
Jeez.
You are all suspects in a murder case,
so you have to find out
who the real culprit is
if you want to clear your names.
First, we'll spend some time in pairs
to examine the crime scene.
There's so much
to unpack and dig into here.
Now, let's begin.
Let's go.
EXAMINING THE SCENE
EVENING OF AUGUST 1, 2018
YEONJIDOL VILLAGE
A BODY WAS FOUND
HANGING BY THE HOSPITAL'S EXTERIOR WALL
JANG JE-IN
IT WAS JANG JE-IN,
DIRECTOR OF YEONJIDOL PSYCHIATRIC HOSPITAL
4TH FLOOR
DIRECTOR'S OFFICE, NURSES' STATION
5TH FLOOR
ROOM 501, ROOM 502
VILLAGE ENTRANCE
YEONJIDOL HOTEL
HANDSOME'S ROOM, JE-IN'S ROOM
VILLAGE HEAD'S HOUSE,
SHAMAN'S SHRINE, SHAMAN'S ROOM
MANNEQUIN FACTORY,
AN DOCTOR'S CAR, YEONJIDOL MOUNTAIN
YEONJIDOL GAS STATION, APIARY
INITIAL EXAMINATION OF CRIME SCENE
COLLECT CLUES FOR 15 MINUTES IN PAIRS
Let's see here.
TEAM 1: KIM HANDSOME & PARK SHAMAN
Ms. Park, could I ask you a favor?
You want me to perform a rite for you?
No, no matter what happens,
please don't fall for me.
Have you lost your mind? Unbelievable.
Look at you, all excited.
We don't have much time. Hurry.
Goodness.
TEAM 3: JANG DETECTIVE & PARK VILLAGE HEAD
I must say, this is a lovely village.
VILLAGE ENTRANCE
The village had an eerie vibe.
There were a couple of big banners
about an upcoming event.
You know how some villages
have something like a motto?
They're usually simple,
like, "Live righteously."
But theirs was more like, "You need to
do this if you want to live here."
Such a code could make the village
more hostile and wary
of anyone and anything
coming from the outside.
DO NOT TRUST ANYONE
Finally, she's down.
My Je-in,
you must've been in so much pain.
- Let's see. Oh gosh.
- Goodness gracious.
What the heck?
She's been completely butchered.
Jeez, seriously.
Who did this to you, Je-in?
Oh my. Hang on, is that a stab wound?
There's a deep cut
right here in the middle.
Doesn't look like a knife wound.
Oh jeez.
The killer really did a number on her.
My goodness, what's this?
Did she get struck in the head?
Or was this from a fall?
Wait a minute,
there's a cut on her arm too.
- Her left arm is almost cut off.
- Just one arm.
How did the body end up there though?
Could she have fallen from the rooftop
after a struggle with her killer
and ended up getting caught
on those wires?
Up there, you know?
DIRECTOR'S OFFICE
I'm going to catch this heartless killer,
no matter what.
Je-in couldn't have done something
so terrible to deserve that.
I'm sure someone
just got the wrong idea about her.
Maybe I'll find evidence
of any misunderstandings in her office.
This place is caked with dust.
SIGNS OF ABANDONMENT
FOUND EVERYWHERE IN THE BUILDING
An envelope.
"Notice of Termination."
She was fired
from the department of psychiatry
in April 2005?
For incompatible values?
Oh, she was fired
from Illyu University Hospital.
HOW DARE THE LIKES OF YOU FIRE ME?
JANG JE-IN WAS FIRED
FROM ILLYU UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL?
Je-in must've been mad about that.
What's this?
JANG JE-IN'S WEDDING PHOTO
Oh, is this the guy
she divorced back then?
Oh, paperwork.
"Subject of investigation, Park Shaman.
Occupation, shaman."
"Family includes Park Father,
a free spirit,
Na Mother, and Park Brother."
So she has a younger brother.
NAME: PARK BROTHER
MEDICAL CONDITION: CONGENITAL BLINDNESS
"An Doctor, orthopedics."
She applied for a job here?
"Podunk Middle School, Podunk High School,
Podunk Medical School."
Employment agreement
between Jang Je-in and An Doctor.
"Must obey all orders
of Director Jang Je-in."
"Forbidden from going out about
in the village."
A monthly salary of only 1.6 million won?
She's a totally broke doctor.
NURSES' STATION
Wait, what?
An Doctor used to work here? What?
There's a nameplate with An Doctor's name
in the nurses' station!
Did she work here?
An Doctor.
"Treatment Log."
"Applied dressing, bruising, antibiotic,
put a cast, faking illness."
She doesn't seem successful enough
to be wearing all that Gucci.
Let's look at the charts.
ADMISSION AND DISCHARGE LOG
NAME: NA TERMINAL
NAME: HAN SURVIVOR
"Anxiety disorder"?
APHASIA, ANXIETY DISORDER
NAME: GO TRIBULATION
DIAGNOSIS: ANXIETY DISORDER
"Eating disorder."
What? Kim Handsome was here too.
NAME: KIM HANDSOME
DEPARTMENT: PSYCHIATRY
5TH FLOOR
ROOM 501, ROOM 502
Something about this place
always brings me to tears.
ROOM 501
My heart started to ache
the moment I went up to the fifth floor.
I couldn't stay there for long.
WHAT IS HIS TEAR-JERKING STORY?
How did the culprit
get up and down the hospital?
There's a flight of stairs.
Oh, there's an elevator too.
ELEVATOR
Does this elevator work?
It should work when I press this.
THE ELEVATOR IS NOT WORKING
The doors don't even open.
SIDE OF THE HOSPITAL BUILDING
FIRE HYDRANT BOX, CIRCUIT BREAKER BOX
FUEL CONTAINER
YEONJIDOL GAS STATION
CAUTION: FLAMMABLE
SELF-SERVICE
Ms. Shaman, you set this up, right?
Yes, with my blood, sweat, and tears.
What kind of rite was it for?
Would you even know if I told you?
I can just feel
there's something suspicious here.
I've never seen this car around here.
She drove a Mercedes, did she?
It's open.
AN DOCTOR'S CAR
PARKED IN FRONT OF THE HOSPITAL
Isn't this a Botte bag?
These are expensive.
INSIDE THE LUXURY DESIGNER BAG
"Vecuronium bromide, potassium chloride."
3 TYPES OF DRUGS IN THE BOX
AN DOCTOR'S PHONE
What's this?
A PLAYLIST OF SONGS?
"Five-minute Meditation"?
You are the best.
You have the hands of a god.
You are your patients' salvation.
This is something only you can do.
You are their savior.
"Savior"?
What's this?
"Jang Je-in." What's this doing in here?
JANG JE-IN'S EMPLOYEE ID
Having the victim's item in possession
makes you the prime suspect.
Jang Je-in's ID found in An Doctor's car.
THE NOTE-TAKING KING OF THE BLOCK
TEXT MESSAGES ON AN DOCTOR'S PHONE
Just 10,000 won?
10,000 WON, PAID IN FULL
YEONJIDOL GAS STATION
AN EMERGENCY TEXT ABOUT THE LANDSLIDE
What's this now?
A MYSTERY VIP?
- I'M RUNNING LATE DUE TO THE LANDSLIDE.
- UNDERSTOOD.
I happened to find
a key piece of evidence.
The GPS app.
23:15 YEONJIDOL LAKE
23:40 YEONJIDOL PSYCHIATRIC HOSPITAL
"Yeonjidol Lake"?
Why did she go to the lake?
Let's think this through.
GOING THROUGH EVERY INCH
OF AN DOCTOR'S CAR
What's this now?
Who's "Na Terminal"?
NA TERMINAL
FLEXIBLE SAVINGS ACCOUNT
The PIN must be 5279.
HOSPITAL FEES: 5,000,000 WON
WITHDRAWAL: 180,000,000 WON
BACK SEAT
Computers are my biggest weakness.
Log-in? "Welcome."
- Detective!
- Yes?
Can you come here for a second?
- I'm useless with computers!
- Sure.
- Man, this lady...
- Yes?
- She's... You know.
- What is it?
DID HE FIND SOMETHING BIG?
What is it?
JOIN US WHEN DATING GETS TOUGH
What's this?
HOLD YOUR BREATH AND LOVE DIVE
MODERATOR: SAVIOR
ESTABLISHED IN AUGUST 3, 2013
ANNOUNCEMENT: HOW TO REQUEST
A RELATIONSHIP CONSULTATION
There's something fishy about this.
A DOCTOR GIVING RELATIONSHIP ADVICE?
ANOTHER ITEM IN THE TRUNK
What's this? A tripod?
A tripod.
IV POLE
I think I've dug up
everything there is on An Doctor.
PROUD
Just you wait.
I'm going to end you.
I'll just...
YEONJIDOL HOTEL
So this is the front desk.
YEONJIDOL HOTEL LOBBY
HOTEL GUEST LIST, ROOM KEYS
JANG JE-IN'S HOTEL ROOM
HANDSOME'S HOTEL ROOM
I find Kim Handsome suspicious.
He's too young to be saying
he's experienced love so deep
that no one would understand.
And he was so empathic about it.
In cases like this, it's always
the boyfriend that's most suspicious.
Handsome is way too suspicious.
A Killer's Mind.
That's when I got the feeling,
"He's someone who'd kill her
if he can't have her."
"TILL DEATH DO US PART"
TRUE LOVE OVERCOMES SUCH LIMITS
He's the worst.
Was he planning to confess his love?
Oh jeez, that scared me. What's that?
Who carries around a medical saw?
Oh, medical supplies.
MEDICAL SUPPLY BAG
Ethanol,
hydrogen peroxide,
formalin.
Formalin? I've heard of it before.
KIM HANDSOME'S WALLET FOUND
JANG JE-IN, KIM HANDSOME
My goodness, what a romantic.
There's a photo.
What's this?
There's something here.
A MYSTERIOUS SELFIE?
What's this?
YEONJIDOL HOTEL RECEIPTS
Dating back to 2014, 2015, 2017,
and 2018.
This guy's a total lunatic.
Those receipts were actually
from when Je-in was gone.
Why was he here when she wasn't?
KIM HANDSOME'S SUITCASE
Was he in the hospital?
SELFIES TAKEN IN THE HOSPITAL
Looks like a hospital.
What's this?
"Seoul District Court Ruling"?
"Kim Handsome, unlawful confinement."
Oh jeez.
What's this now?
SCRAPBOOK
"April 1, 2009."
I MET HER FOR THE FIRST TIME
THE KISS SHE LEFT ME, MWAH♡
That's so creepy.
What's this?
"The moment I met you, I was born again."
He did seem a bit stalkerish.
THE SWEETNESS OF OUR LOVE
WILL LAST FOREVER
I think this love was one-sided.
Was Handsome really her boyfriend?
WERE THEY REALLY IN A RELATIONSHIP?
What? There's no ring in this box.
Oh my gosh!
What's wrong with you?
You opened the door yourself, didn't you?
Why act all scared?
I can't do this anymore.
That's too much!
That freaked me out.
IN THE CLOSET
IS A MYSTERIOUS MANNEQUIN
For goodness' sake. I hate this.
Wait, what's this?
SITE OF EVE FESTIVAL IN FRONT OF THE HOTEL
What's this?
It's Village Head's phone.
"Kim Village, youth association leader"?
"Mr. Village Head, where did you go?"
He didn't stick around?
Where was he off to?
Where did he go?
Park Village Head was the one person
I had implicit trust in
among my fellow villagers.
But this time, I'll have to
take a look in his place.
THE HEAD OF A VILLAGE KNOWN FOR ITS HONEY
BEEKEEPING SUPPLIES
I just knew
there was something fishy about him.
He still has these at his house?
SIGNS USED TO PROTEST
AGAINST THE PSYCHIATRIC HOSPITAL
Why was he so against it?
THE NEWS IS MAKING MY FISTS SHAKE!
Well, looks like Park Village Head
owns plenty of sharp things too.
A SMORGASBORD OF WEAPONS
Let's check out his room.
Beekeeping, honey,
several awards of appreciation.
AWARD OF MERIT
AWARD OF APPRECIATION
PARK VILLAGE HEAD'S BEEKEEPING BUSINESS
CONTRIBUTED TO THE GROWTH OF THE VILLAGE
AWARD OF APPRECIATION
This must be his mother.
A PHOTO WITH HIS MOTHER WHEN HE WAS YOUNG?
Is there something more to this too?
YEONJIDOL NEWS
He was suspicious from the start,
going on and on
about fairness and whatnot.
"EVERYONE WILL BE EQUALLY PROSPEROUS
IN MY VILLAGE."
A NEW ITEM DISCOVERED IN THE CLOSET
What's this?
This guy went to college?
ILLYU UNIVERSITY VARSITY JACKET
What kind of college graduate
spells "coming soon" as "comeing sun"?
ENGLISH SKILLS OF A GRADUATE OF ILLYU,
A TOP-TIER UNIVERSITY?
"Comeing sun"?
- What are you up to?
- It's none of your business, okay?
I'm heading to the mannequin factory.
What for?
Why would you go there?
MANNEQUIN FACTORY
MANNEQUIN FACTORY RUN BY JANG COUSIN
Is he making mannequins in this factory
or breaking them apart?
Who even uses mannequins these days?
Why would he insist on running
that mannequin factory in this village
right in front of the abandoned hospital?
He could've easily killed her with these.
(WHAM)
"Sales ledger by year."
YEAR, REVENUE, EXPENSES, NET PROFIT
I see he was about to
go out of business, huh?
SHOULD I SHUT IT DOWN...?
"Payment Past Due Letter."
20 MILLION WON OVERDUE
He was drowning in debt.
ANOTHER ITEM FOUND IN ANOTHER DRAWER
"Leak Test Report."
So the mannequin factory...
It seems there was a leak
in the hospital.
So there was a leak in the hospital.
What's this?
"Real Estate Sales Agreement."
I see he was trying to buy the hospital.
NAME OF THE SELLER: ?
NAME OF PURCHASER: JANG COUSIN
Oh jeez! That scared me.
INSIDE THE MANNEQUIN'S HEAD
What's this?
"Viagura."
Why are they all wet?
THE PILLS ARE WET FOR SOME REASON?
OTHER SIDE OF THE FACTORY
JANG COUSIN'S TINY ROOM
So he did scarf down some kimchi.
DOES THIS MATCH HIS ALIBI TESTIMONY?
JANG COUSIN'S PHONE
"Don't contact me. You piss me off."
JANG JE-IN
He didn't say anything about
exchanging texts with her.
That's right, Je-in's family
was really well-off.
JANG JE-IN'S HOUSE
JANG COUSIN'S HOUSE
JANG COUSIN'S FATHER
JANG TROUBLEMAKER
He looks just like his father.
Family and Inheritance Law? What's this?
"Will."
A WILL?
His father didn't get any inheritance
because he was disowned.
I found a goldmine of clues.
AN EXPERIENCED INVESTIGATOR
IMMEDIATELY CHECKS THE CUSHION
"Waiver."
"If I can't repay the money..."
What's this about both eyes and kidneys?
He pledges to compensate
by forfeiting body parts?
He must've been under a lot of stress.
SHAMAN'S SHRINE, SHAMAN'S ROOM
I should go through Shaman's room too.
So this is a real shrine. Goodness.
She's worshipping every god there is,
from Buddha to the Great Jade Emperor.
ALL SORTS OF GODS IN ONE PLACE
Oh boy.
PARK SHAMAN'S SHRINE
People usually hide things in...
Oh, look. There's a safe.
SAFE
This safe is... Wait, 1991?
COULD THAT BE THE PASSCODE?
Hey, it's open.
SAFE OPEN
I opened the safe.
- Hey, Ms. Park Shaman.
- Yes?
I opened your safe.
What? How did you figure out the passcode?
You have a lot of gold bars in here.
- Hey! Don't touch my money!
- Oh my.
What's this, a ledger?
PARK SHAMAN'S LEDGER
I see it has her clients' information.
Why did the total amount go down
from 500 million won to 300?
What's this? "First eye transplant surgery
including optic nerve
successfully performed in the US"?
JOHNS HOPKANGS UNIV.'S SUCCESS
IN EYE AND OPTIC NERVE TRANSPLANT SURGERY
"Huge waiting list
despite a 500-million-won price tag."
This is...
AN EARTHENWARE POT
IN FRONT OF THE BUDDHA STATUE
What's this supposed to be?
These are earphones.
Jeez. What's this now?
WORN CLOTHING
Seriously, what is this?
PARK SHAMAN'S ROOM
This lady, I swear...
Wait.
What's this photo?
There's a kid who's visually impaired.
A VISUALLY IMPAIRED CHILD?
Go High Shaman's Secret Book of Rites.
I guess shamans have to
learn their trade from books too.
They have an instruction manual of sorts.
That's quite amusing.
INSIDE PARK SHAMAN'S CLOSET
Oh jeez, what's this?
A BOX WITH A KNIFE STUCK ON IT
What's this?
I see what it is.
Judging by the knife on the box,
she must've cursed someone.
Wait, who's this?
PARK SHAMAN
"E-Ryu University School of Medicine."
Her boyfriend must've been a doctor.
Who is he?
HE LOOKS FAMILIAR
IN THE ENVELOPE
"Notice of Education Committee Ruling."
She slipped a mouse
in her friend's backpack.
That got her expelled?
"Jang Je-in"? So my Je-in sued you!
"My Je-in"?
- Examination time is over.
- All right, I got it.
- What do you mean?
- You have to leave now.
But I need to catch the dang killer!
- You have to leave.
- To where?
- This way, please.
- This is my village!
- Sir, please don't.
- I was born and raised here.
- Not right now. Your 15 minutes are up.
- Got that?
COMBINE THE CLUES
Now, you must've examined the scene
you found most suspicious.
A BRIEFING BASED ON CLUES FOUND
Jeez, stop crying.
It's messing up your face.
SOAKING WET
You're overreacting.
The truth's going to come out now.
I was hoping to ask you to go first,
Mr. Kim Handsome.
- Are you up for it?
- Have you collected yourself?
- Why wouldn't he be?
- I can go first.
I have to say one thing first.
- I'm just so heartbroken, you see.
- Yes?
So I'd like us all to have
a moment of silence in honor of Je-in.
A moment of silence for Je-in.
O gods of heaven and earth...
ONE OF THEM IS SUPPOSEDLY HONORING
THE PERSON THEY KILLED
He's a complete nutjob.
All right.
I first went to see how my Je-in looked
in her final moments.
But it looked like
she was stabbed more than a dozen times.
She was punctured on both shoulders,
shanked in the thigh,
shanked in the shin,
and shanked in the chest too.
- Do you have to say "shanked"?
- Sorry.
Which butcher sells these shanks
you speak of?
- Say "stabbed."
- Okay, "stabbed."
Anyway, she had a lot of stab wounds
and also a massive wound
on the back of her head.
And it didn't look like the killer
finished her off instantly.
- Here's what I think.
- Please go on.
The victim must've ended up on the roof
one way or another.
- Agreed.
- For the killer
to take her up there without a struggle,
she must've been unconscious.
If she wasn't drugged,
that blow to the back of the head
could've done it.
- But wouldn't that have left bloodstains?
- Right, there should be bloodstains.
- I went up to the roof myself.
- Okay.
Yes, you're the only one
who went up there.
- How did you go up there?
- There's a door off to the side.
- I see.
- Does that door not lock?
- Is it always unlocked?
- It's unlocked, yes.
So this is the way to the roof. All right.
I went up the roof,
and I figured with such wounds,
the roof would be a bloody mess.
But when I got there...
What the heck?
Did they not fight here?
It was clean.
Squeaky clean.
Not even a single drop of blood.
Okay, then let's go check there later
and figure out what happened.
Sure.
So then I went to the director's office
- where my Je-in used to work.
- Right.
I looked through the drawers
- and found that she'd hired someone.
- Hired someone?
Yes, to dig up information on someone,
who turned out to be...
Ms. Park Shaman.
It has all the details about your life.
- She dug up my information?
- What?
It says your hobby
is doing 24-hour rite challenges.
It even covers what your ideal type is.
My ideal type? Even I don't know that.
You're just being shy.
Your ideal type is a man
who's 180 cm tall with long hair.
- No way.
- Oh, is that so?
WHO COULD IT BE?
Let me tell you once again.
- Please don't fall for me.
- I hate this.
Anyway, it had information
about Park Shaman and her family,
including Park Father, Na Mother,
and even her younger brother.
- Why would she do that?
- But she had no reason to do that.
- So that's why I went to the shrine.
- Okay.
I found a box
in her closet with a knife
stuck on top of it.
I opened it up
and found dolls like these inside.
Now, I couldn't help but wonder
who she cursed with these voodoo dolls.
- Well, there were photos.
- Really?
There was a man
- who looked very familiar in those photos.
- Right.
I thought back
and remembered the wedding photo
- in Je-in's office.
- The wedding photo.
It was the same man.
You know,
as the youngsters say these days,
there was an "overlap."
- Sort of like monkey branching?
- He left me for her, okay?
What else was I supposed to do?
I had to curse them.
- I couldn't just sit back and watch.
- My goodness.
You cursed him because he left you?
I also found a document in there.
It was about her expulsion
from high school.
She apparently slipped a mouse
in her friend's backpack,
almost giving the friend a heart attack.
So she got expelled.
I basically got kicked out
because of Je-in.
- Right.
- Yeah.
That must've started
the bad blood between them.
There must've been a backstory
as to why she slipped that mouse in.
She must've resented Je-in
for losing the man she loved to her.
But then again, Je-in also ran
a background check on Park Shaman.
So I'm pretty sure they've had
some sort of grudge against each other.
Then I remembered what I saw
in the background check report
and looked through it.
It turns out her younger brother
is visually impaired.
Her brother is blind,
but he had a chance to get the surgery
for 500 million won.
So she performed rites and sold talismans
to save up 500 million won,
but something must've gone wrong.
So I was wondering
what that could've been,
and then found out that my Je-in sued her.
What?
"Jang Je-in"? So my Je-in sued you!
ANOTHER DOCUMENT IN THE CURSE BOX
"You're sentenced to pay
170 million won in taxes,
30 million in fines,
and a 2-month business suspension."
THE RULING
She must've performed a rite
by the hospital
and disrupted the business.
So all the taxes and fines
- amounted to exactly 200 million won.
- 200 million won.
She worked so hard to earn money
to pay for her brother's eye surgery,
but she lost 200 million of that money
because my Je-in sued her.
That's motive for sure.
- She loves her brother dearly.
- Oh dear.
So you decided to go all in on me, huh?
Yes, unfortunately for you.
SORRY, BUT YES
- I'm afraid that's the case.
- Have a seat, Mr. Kim Handsome.
Now, since you were attacked so much,
- it should be your turn, Park Shaman.
- Shall I begin my rite?
Are you going to attack me now?
Are you ready to be cursed?
Let me load up on some tears first.
- We have this thing called intuition, no?
- Sure.
- It can be important.
- I was walking along
and it led me to Mr. Kim Handsome's room
at the hotel.
- Now, there's a matchup.
- A counterpunch, I see.
I went where the spirits guided me,
and what did I find?
A hint suggesting
he didn't get to tell her how he felt.
A ring box.
- A ring box?
- That's right.
But it was empty.
Where could this ring have gone?
And there were wine glasses
left untouched on the table.
So it was all just for himself.
A one-sided love.
- But--
- Alone in love
- You know that song, right?
- That's enough of that.
- What's that ring?
- Let me apologize.
Did you give her the ring?
- I did.
- You did?
Did she have a ring on her finger?
No, she didn't.
I'm pretty sure she tossed the ring.
The ring is probably somewhere
around the crime scene.
We have to find the engagement ring
that she tossed.
Then, I looked through his wallet
and found hotel receipts.
- Hotel receipts?
- Receipts...
But then, I noticed something strange.
For five straight years
from July 31, 2014,
he stayed at this hotel
every year on July 31st.
- July 31st?
- Suspicious indeed.
Why did he stay there?
You know,
no matter how many
shamanic rites I perform,
I'm never spooked.
That was until I opened
Mr. Kim Handsome's closet.
There's something else?
- A mannequin.
- What?
There was a mannequin
wearing a white dress.
- A mannequin?
- I saw that mannequin too.
Didn't it look like my Je-in?
- That's why it's creepy.
- I'm the mannequin expert here.
Be honest. What were your plans?
- Something perverted?
- Explain.
You want me to be honest?
I was going to take commemorative photos.
- For photoshopping?
- What photos?
- Commemorative photos.
- Maybe he practiced stabbing it?
REHEARSING THE CRIME WITH THE MANNEQUIN?
A rehearsal for murder?
Were the two of them
even in a real relationship?
Where did you meet Ms. Jang Je-in?
You met as a doctor and a patient,
didn't you?
To be completely honest,
I received some treatment a while back
for alcohol addiction.
See? They started off on the wrong foot.
What's so wrong about it?
Why can't a patient
and a doctor be in love?
Did you love her, or did you stalk her?
Be honest.
We were in love.
But here's the conclusive evidence
- that Mr. Kim Handsome
- There's more?
is a perverted nutjob.
What's this?
"Seoul District Court Ruling"?
"Kim Handsome, unlawful confinement."
Oh jeez.
He's already a criminal.
You served three years for kidnapping
and unlawful confinement, right?
Who did you kidnap?
- Who do you think?
- I didn't kidnap her.
Je-in and I just had an argument...
If you were her boyfriend,
she wouldn't have reported you.
We were in a relationship,
but I lost my head a little, so--
Did you hit her?
How could you say that?
I would never do something like that.
I only held a pair of scissors
that happened to be next to me
as I talked to her.
It was a petty argument between a couple,
but people misunderstood it
and made it out to be more serious
than it really was.
So it was perverse confinement.
Well...
I don't think I need to
explain myself any further.
People mistook my love
for something else all my life.
I WAS WAITING FOR BEAUTY AND HER
COLLEAGUES STARTED PICKING A FIGHT...
KIM HANDSOME'S PAST DIARY
Since then, I always approached love
thinking that we can overcome anything
as long as my feelings
and the other person's feelings are true.
Other people's misunderstandings
are nothing new to me.
You could say I've gotten used to it.
But unlike Mr. Kim Handsome here,
I don't just go after one person.
- Oh dear.
- An Doctor?
- Yes?
- You drove a white Mercedes here, right?
- Yes, it's mine.
- It's your car, correct?
You sound so proud and insufferable.
- It's not much, but it's mine.
- Did you get it on a payment plan?
- No, I paid upfront with cash.
- At once and in cash?
Good for you.
Anyway, I found these in the back seat.
Since you're a medical professional,
you could easily kill someone you hate
with these drugs.
- In her car?
- Why did you bring those?
I always make house calls,
so I need to carry certain drugs--
You took the Hippocratic Oath
as a doctor, right?
- I did, yes.
- Can these drugs kill a person if misused?
Well, excessive use of any drugs
can be dangerous.
So you admit one can die
from excessive use of these?
But consider the body.
- The cause of death can't be drugs.
- It's possible.
In order to make that happen as a woman,
you'd first have to
make the victim unconscious.
Come on, Mr. Kim Handsome.
This isn't your first rodeo.
I wouldn't know
since I haven't killed anyone yet.
THE SPIRITS ARE CLUCKING IN DISAPPROVAL
- That's all from me.
- All right.
- Got it.
- Good work.
- Let's move on to An Doctor.
- Sure.
Your outfit is so flashy.
It's making my eyes sting.
This is what success looks like.
I found quite a lot of evidence.
- Just how many pictures did you take?
- Oh my.
She brought a whole photo album.
First off,
I looked into Mr. Kim Handsome too.
- Me?
- That's right.
- It's Handsome again.
- I'm sorry, but...
I'd appreciate it if you stopped
showing so much interest in me.
Be quiet.
Before I talk about Mr. Handsome,
let's discuss the corpse first.
It's true that she was slashed,
but I focused on the wound on her wrist.
It looked like the killer
tried to cut her hand off.
It was cut halfway through,
leaving her wrist dangling.
- Her left hand?
- Yes, the left hand,
the hand you usually
wear a wedding ring on.
But I also noticed something
about the mannequin earlier.
- You just took note of itself, didn't you?
- Yes.
- The mannequin's left hand was cut off.
- Are you serious?
No way.
Was he trying to swap it
with Je-in's left hand?
- Exactly.
- Because she wasn't wearing the ring!
What? It's missing a hand.
What's this?
Why did he cut the hand off?
A HANDLESS MANNEQUIN ON THE WALL
THE VICTIM'S PARTLY CUT LEFT HAND
AND THE MANNEQUIN'S CUT LEFT HAND?
Why cut off a hand?
- Why did you cut this hand?
- What a lunatic.
Why did you cut it off?
He practiced cutting it on that mannequin.
I was thinking
that since Ms. Jang tossed the ring,
maybe he wanted to take her hand
to put the ring on it
- and keep it forever.
- So he practiced.
That's an excellent deduction.
It's not nearly as serious as you think.
- It was just another minor argument.
- It's serious.
Did you cut it off
because she wouldn't take your ring?
Well, I did put my ring
- on Je-in's finger.
- On her hand?
But she just took it off
and tossed it away,
so I got upset.
You took out your anger on the mannequin?
That's what happened.
But I'm not the kind of person
who would hurt someone.
- It might be better if you were.
- Just curse them instead or something.
Why'd you even bring
a mannequin to a hotel?
I may run a mannequin factory,
but mannequins are basically humans.
- What the heck are you saying?
- What's that supposed to mean?
- There's more on Mr. Handsome.
- Please stop.
I noticed something in the photos
you carry in your wallet.
There was a photo
where your eyelids were red and swollen
- like you just had double eyelid surgery.
- That's true.
Did you get surgery?
No, not at all.
That photo was taken
after Je-in and I Netflix and chilled
five years ago.
- Oh, really?
- Must we really know that?
- Sorry for oversharing.
- That's too much information.
- Anyhow, so?
- We were drinking wine together
and I blacked out at some point.
When I woke up the next day, my whole body
was aching with bruises everywhere,
and my clothes were all messed up.
- Whose?
- Mine.
I couldn't remember anything,
but I figured I spent
a passionate night with Je-in.
- So I took a selfie to document pure joy.
- Unbelievable.
Am I speaking another language?
What's "Netflix and chill"?
- You don't...
- What does it mean?
You don't know what it means?
- So what, you spent the night together?
- It's what the kids say these days.
It means--
No, not that.
- They were hitting each other?
- What the heck are you talking about?
- What?
- Goodness, hitting's involved?
I told you, I'm not a pervert!
But why were both your eyes bruised
like you got double eyelid surgery?
I don't know because I blacked out.
I guess it got really passionate,
and we got a little rough with each other.
- So gross.
- If that's your idea of passion,
- you should take up martial arts.
- This will surely anger the gods.
All right then.
Thanks for your testimony, Mr. Handsome.
Next up...
Jang Cousin!
- That came out of nowhere.
- Me?
It's rare to have someone yell like that
and no one in the room be startled.
It's you, Jang Cousin!
Just humor her. Try again.
- Jang Cousin!
- Oh jeez!
What do you want?
- First, let's look at his roots.
- I have nothing to hide.
I saw his family photo.
If you see here, there's a clear contrast.
You must've grown up feeling jealous
of your cousin's wealth and resented her.
Then, I found Jang Grandpa's will.
According to it,
Jang Cousin's dad was disowned,
so he couldn't get any inheritance.
So that's why only his family was so poor.
Surely he had an inferiority complex.
- Come on, that's not true.
- He must've been so jealous and angry.
He even had books
on family and inheritance law.
It looks like he's very interested in laws
related to getting inheritance.
- Are you serious?
- Those were my father's books.
But what's even more suspicious
is that there's a leak test report.
And where's the source of that leak?
Jang Je-in's hospital.
I kept getting water leaks in my factory,
so I tested it and found out it was
coming from the hospital, that's all.
An ill-fated relationship, indeed.
And what got wet in the mannequin factory?
- Can you tell me?
- Got wet?
My eyes, obviously.
I teared up big time,
reminiscing the good old days.
I mean, if there was a leak,
something must've gotten wet.
It wasn't just the mannequins
that got wet in the factory.
Inside those mannequins
- were Viagura pills--
- Who told you to look through that stuff?!
- Jeez, you scared me.
- You dirty old man!
- Wait, Viagura?
- Goodness.
- Gosh, it's hot in here.
- But the Viagura wasn't for himself.
- Was he selling them?
- There was a huge supply of it.
- He had way too much.
- I see it now.
- So he's a smuggler.
- I never understood
why you ran a mannequin factory
in the middle of nowhere.
- Fine, I'll just come clean,
- How gross.
since we have Jang Detective here and all.
At first, I ran an honest business
with my mannequin factory.
The business was good
with all the shopping malls in Dongdaemun
all those years ago.
But those places started to die out
- so my sales took a hit.
- And only guys like him buy mannequins.
Exactly.
My one and only customer.
Then...
Was it five years ago?
A friend came up to me and asked
if I'd be interested in a side gig.
He said it was smuggling and that
I only had to hide stuff in my mannequins
and transport them.
That's all there is.
You didn't take them yourself?
- But I did find...
- What good would it do me?
- I found a pill on your desk.
- How revolting.
It was for a clinical trial!
I can't just send them out to my clients
without testing them!
That's not how I do business.
- Gosh, it's hot.
- All right.
Okay, I get it.
I have another question.
I saw that you were looking to buy
Ms. Jang's land for 500 million won.
Why would I buy from her
if I wanted to kill her?
I could've just killed her.
- But--
- I bet she turned down your offer.
- Correct. He asked...
- She really is a shaman.
- Of course, I am.
- You really are.
He asked and she said,
"Family? Please. Don't contact me."
You know nothing!
That was the text Ms. Jang Je-in sent.
I don't think they were close enough
to even be called family.
He probably texted her to get her to sign
the real estate sales agreement.
But Jang Cousin doesn't have the money
to buy the land in the first place.
The mannequin factory
wasn't doing great at all,
and because of the leak,
he now had to sign over his organs
unless he could pay back his creditors.
So why did he want to
buy this land so much?
Perhaps he needs that land
because there's something buried there.
A lot of you will regret it
once I start talking.
I wonder if you're prepared for that.
We've been doing this for over a decade,
and his character hasn't changed a bit.
Too much change means it's time to die.
So... Wait a minute.
Since you're a doctor,
let me ask you something.
I heard there's a disorder called...
What was it again?
Erotic...
- What? Erotic?
- Erotic?
Erotic maniac?
It was erotic...
It was something like that.
I won't know
unless you tell me the exact name.
Erotic...
- Stop saying that, you pervert!
- Erotic what?
It's the name of the disorder.
- Excuse me?
- What was it again? It was six syllables.
Oh, I got it!
It was "erotomania."
"Erotomania"?
Yes, erotomania.
You'd know since you're a doctor, right?
Actually, I'm an orthopedist.
ONLY ORTHOPEDICS FOR ME
Sure, I suppose it's possible
for a doctor not to know it.
So what is this erotomania, you ask?
"You're looking at me."
What? Me?
"Are you that attracted to me?"
What a crazy bastard.
- That's what erotomania is!
- Wow, okay.
That's completely nuts.
It's him!
He told me earlier to move my leg
and stop seducing him.
He told me not to fall for him.
So I checked to see
why you were like that,
- Handsome.
- I only say those things
- because women keep falling for me.
- Kim Handsome
was a patient here
at this psychiatric hospital!
- Erotomania.
- Alcohol addiction?
- Right.
- That's what he told us.
But he didn't mention his erotomania,
an even more serious disorder!
That's why even if a woman
simply looks at him,
he thinks that she likes him.
If a woman merely asks if he's okay,
he immediately thinks
that she cares about him.
He lives his life
trapped in that delusion.
What are you taking notes for?
Stop writing about me, ladies.
You can't have Shaman!
- What was that for?
- That came out of nowhere.
- I just wanted to try something.
- For goodness' sake.
- You can have her.
- I'm so sick of this.
Let me ask this. Who do we have
to thank for our village's growth
and the comfortable life we enjoy?
Who do we owe it to?
Why, the Great Park Village Head,
of course.
Sounds like "the Great Leader Comrade."
Everyone, give him a round of applause.
- Why should I? I'm not from here.
- Everyone who lives here
should applaud him.
- She's the only other resident here.
- I agree, but we shouldn't worship him.
However, this is the last time
I'll be clapping for him.
- You told us to clap, and now it's over?
- What a twist.
- Unbelievable.
- Let's see.
Mr. Village Head,
did you attend university?
- What?
- Did you attend university?
- No, I didn't.
- You didn't?
That can't be.
I found a varsity jacket in your closet.
Didn't you attend Illyu University?
Having a varsity jacket
doesn't mean you went there.
Come to think of it,
Je-in is the only one in this village
who went to that prestigious university.
- Is that Je-in's jacket?
- You're right.
- Exactly!
- No, well...
Je-in worked at Illyu University Hospital.
I'm a shaman, okay?
- The gods are truly with you.
- Look here.
I'm 187 cm.
You think a woman's jacket would fit me?
So you're saying
this varsity jacket isn't yours?
It wasn't mine back then.
Wait, Mr. Jang Cousin.
As for the Illyu varsity jacket...
Well, to be honest,
I just got it a while ago
from someone.
I don't really remember how I got it,
but I did.
I was wondering
why a guy who went to Illyu
wouldn't know how to spell "coming soon."
He wrote "comeing sun" instead.
I wanted the sun to come, okay?
- Oh, I can see that.
- That makes sense too.
- Let's not be too prejudicial.
- All right.
I apologize for not understanding
our great and wonderful Mr. Village Head.
That's what you thought I'd say, huh?
You won't be able to deny this!
He has anger issues.
- Try me!
- What is it?
- I looked through his phone.
- You see...
- Oh dear.
- Goodness.
It's Village Head's phone.
"Mr. Village Head..." That came at 8:50 p.m.
"Where did you go? You have to be here
before the opening ceremony."
What? Where did he go?
Where were you and what were you doing?
- The psychiatric hospital?
- Where were you on the eve festival?
I had kimchi and soju in my room.
I was busy going around
from place to place.
I even went up the mountain a few times.
When the youth association leader
was waiting for you to give the speech?
I swung by my place
to take care of some business as well.
That's all. Why?
Oh, is that so?
If you ask why,
I don't know how to answer--
Come at me. Bring it on.
- That's terrifying.
- I can't do that.
- That's hilarious.
- I was nearly a goner there.
Normally, I may seem like
a total brown-noser to that Village Head,
but I'm more than that!
He says he went home
and to the mountain and whatnot,
but why would he do all that
when the eve festival was going on?
It's probably because he had to
grab something from home
to hide something up in the mountains.
Village Head has a secret
that he can't tell other people.
When I went to his room earlier
and saw the map of the merging villages
that said "comeing sun,"
I thought, "Is he trying to build
a kingdom of his own?"
That thought just came to me.
But the only person who left the village
to study and experience the outside world
was Je-in, you know?
So it got me thinking that maybe
she brought something new to this place
that prevented him
from creating his kingdom.
You know how this village
is all about fairness and equality.
YEONJIDOL VILLAGE CODE OF CONDUCT
- And that--
- Hey!
I stopped Yeonjidol's former village head
when he embezzled all that money!
And I built this place into what it is now
with my beekeeping business for ten years!
I even made
the merger with Banjidol happen.
That's why I have these bags
under my eyes!
- Yes, you're absolutely right.
- Right?
- I'm so sorry.
- How dare you?
Just seeing how furious he got
at the thought of any harm
coming to the village he's the head of,
it really felt like he saw this place
as his own kingdom.
So if Jang Je-in had done anything
to tarnish his great legacy,
cause serious harm to it,
or something along those lines,
he might've experienced emotional turmoil
that would've been enough motive
to commit murder.
First of all,
I also went all in on one person.
- On whom?
- I'm scared.
- It's...
- Not me, right?
An Doctor.
- Thank the gods of heaven and earth.
- I knew it.
- She seemed fishy.
- Why me?
- I saw An Doctor's résumé.
- What of it?
She doesn't look like it,
but she's from the countryside too.
What?
- She was born in the country.
- Got a new identity?
The first hospital she worked at
was Samryu University Hospital.
Isn't that the place
where you can only leave inside a coffin?
- She first worked at Samryu,
- It's not like that.
- but then worked at the prestigious Illyu.
- A transfer?
- From 2002 to 2012,
- She's very ambitious.
you worked at Illyu University Hospital.
How did that happen?
Well...
A hospital director that I know
got me a job there
in exchange for prescribing
whatever drugs they wanted--
And who was that director?
One of my acquaintances.
- Just someone you know?
- Yes.
Is that where you first met her?
- I mean Jang Je-in.
- Yes.
How long did you work together?
- Exactly three years, right?
- Yes, that sounds about right.
After that, Jang Je-in got fired.
But then, out of the blue,
you quit your job
at Illyu University Hospital in 2013
and came to work
at Yeonjidol Psychiatric Hospital.
Why was that?
Why did you come here?
Well, for reasons of her own,
Je-in invited me here to work together.
I know.
- That's why.
- You got kicked out of Illyu
because of malpractice.
COURT FINDS DOCTOR NEGLIGENT
AFTER A 9-MONTH TRIAL
- Malpractice, huh? Unbelievable.
- That left her no choice whatsoever.
Was your medical license
revoked back then?
- No, it wasn't.
- Okay.
But it was a huge scandal
and even made it on the news.
I read an article about it.
I was blacklisted.
How do you have the gall
to walk around so shamelessly?
- Did your patient die?
- I have something to say about that.
I feel so wronged,
so I have to tell you this.
As you heard, I'm from the sticks,
so no one treated me
like an equal at Illyu.
The patient was already dead
by the time they went under,
but the hospital just made me
the scapegoat.
So you think they threw you under the bus
because you were from the countryside?
That's why they asked me to the OR.
It's not that I'm a bad doctor.
- It's just so unfair.
- A rite will help you feel better.
- Thank you.
- Give me a call sometime.
But you see,
I saw two emails on your laptop
exchanged between Jang Je-in
and someone named Park Colleague.
Here's their conversation.
It reads, "I need a stand-in.
Who'd be a good fit?"
"How about that girl
who worked at Illyu University Hospital?"
"Isn't she perfect for a stand-in?"
And then Je-in writes,
"The stand-in is too dumb.
I'll have to fire her."
Are you the dumb stand-in?
- What's that?
- Nod if it's true.
Come on, An Stand-in.
I knew it.
- So she was the stand-in.
- But Je-in sent records
- of these email exchanges to An Doctor.
- To An Doctor?
Why did she do that?
- I was the one who sent it.
- What?
I sent it to myself using Je-in's laptop.
- Of course.
- So I could sue her.
- To have as evidence of them conspiring?
- To sue her?
- You secretly peeped in on her laptop?
- Yes.
- I forwarded it to myself.
- After killing her?
- No, of course not.
- I see, all right.
I also found her employment agreement.
- Her monthly pay
- Yes?
- was a measly 1.6 million won.
- What?
She had to sleep
and eat at the hospital too.
And her treatment log
was filled with only minor tasks.
Her self-esteem probably took a big hit
because of that.
Then five years later,
she becomes a completely different woman.
This stand-in doctor who got paid pennies
now lives a luxurious life,
driving around in a Mercedes.
What happened in those five years?
It's not that something happened.
- People began to realize my capabilities.
- You can't find employment elsewhere.
People just realized
what a good doctor I was.
Do you remember texting a VIP
on August 1st?
- I do.
- Do you always
meet your VIP clients that late?
They're VIPs, after all,
so I go whenever they need me.
I'm dying to know
what An Doctor does with a VIP patient.
The most important part
is that I found the bank book
of a patient named Na Terminal.
- This is...
- And I actually found it hidden
in the seatback pocket
of the passenger seat.
- Of course, I hid it. It's money.
- Did you embezzle your patients' money?
Why would you hide it
when it's not your money?
The same amount of money
was withdrawn every time, until July 30th,
when 180 million won
was withdrawn at once.
At once?
- O spirits, where is Na Terminal now?
- How shameless.
And another thing.
This is what I'm most curious about.
At 9:55 p.m., she fills up her car
at Yeonjidol Gas Station.
She drives a Mercedes,
yet she only got 10,000 won worth of fuel.
- Just 10,000 won?
- Yeah.
She must be flat broke.
- Can't you see what I'm wearing?
- Either she's broke,
or her next stop was a very short drive.
So I looked at her GPS app,
and she entered Yeonjidol Lake
as a destination at 11:15 p.m.
and then Yeonjidol Hospital at 11:40 p.m.
That fits within the window
of the time of death.
- Between 10:20 p.m. and 11:30 p.m.
- Oh, to dump the body?
- That's likely.
- But she failed.
She went to the lake,
but for whatever reason,
she couldn't dump it there.
We have a lot to question her on.
Who is her VIP patient?
Why did she go to the lake?
Why did she only get 10,000 won worth
of fuel when she drives a Mercedes?
And what kind of orthopedic
makes house calls?
Anyway, I'm going to
keep questioning An Doctor
since she can't lie about the facts.
Wait, no, she can do that
if she's the culprit!
Man, what do I do?
So, Park Shaman.
I guess it was your younger brother
in that photo.
Then this may be a delicate subject,
but where is your brother now?
Actually, it's been a few years
- since my brother went missing.
- What?
- Missing?
- That's right.
- It was absolute chaos.
- So he went missing, huh?
Especially given that
he's visually impaired.
Inside your earthenware pot,
I found a T-shirt, a paper doll,
and earphones.
- Earphones?
What are these for?
Oh, those.
In my line of work, I'm often asked
to pray for the dead to reach paradise.
Some items are from my clients,
and some are of my own.
I just store all of them in that pot.
So you keep the stuff in there,
- including the paper doll and earphones?
- Yes, I just keep them in there.
And which one of those is Je-in's?
What?
Her stuff isn't in there.
- Why would it be?
- But Je-in's things--
She's not naive enough
to fall for questions like that.
Don't play cheap tricks on her.
Okay, I see.
- Nice try though.
- Let's move on.
I was more drawn to the corpse,
so I examined it with Mr. Village Head.
How do you think the killer
brought the victim upstairs?
- There are stairs and an elevator.
- If you ask me,
I don't think she was carried up there.
I think they went up together.
That's one possibility.
I noticed a wheelchair
in the other corner of the hospital.
Did anyone else see one?
- It was in the yard.
- There was one, yes.
And what about the elevator?
- I saw it.
- But it's out of service.
- Right?
- Yes, it wasn't working.
But the killer could've cut the power
after killing the victim.
- The building's abandoned, so...
- So the power's out?
- It hasn't worked for ages.
- Okay.
But the cause of death
is severe blood loss.
The victim bled to death
while she was caught in the wires.
The blood loss killed her.
But I don't think
that's how the killer wanted her to die.
Which made me wonder,
"What kind of finale
was the killer picturing?"
That wasn't part of the plan.
But here,
let's think about the container
with 10,000 won worth of fuel.
- Huh?
- What?
- I found the container
- I got chills.
by the hospital building.
I was so shocked by it.
So she didn't fill up her car.
She just bought a container of fuel.
- The container, yes.
- Right.
Okay, let me tell you why I only filled up
10,000 won worth of fuel in my car.
As I'm sure you know from my text,
I only went to the gas station
after texting
that the landslide was making me run late.
I didn't have much time to begin with.
How could I stand there
and fill up 150,000 won worth of fuel
when I was already running late
for my VIP patient?
I'm not so shameless as that.
- My VIP patient was waiting.
- But if you drive a Mercedes,
you'd fill up more than that
because it doesn't get you far.
- Have you driven a Mercedes?
- You know?
- Sorry?
- Do you own one?
- No, I don't.
- Well, I do.
And I only fill up 10,000 won.
Has any of you driven a Mercedes?
I doubt it. You're all country bumpkins.
- Have you ever even been to Seoul?
- I have!
- I did my initiation rite in Seoul, okay?
- I've been there!
- Stop talking about things you don't know.
- You'd better remember that.
I only got 10,000 won worth of fuel
because I was in a hurry.
Have you seen someone in a hurry
take their time to fill up the tank?
I have!
- Where?
- In a movie.
- Exactly.
- Jeez.
- This is so frustrating.
- She's finally showing her true colors.
- Everybody finds their voice in this room.
- So the loudest person wins here, huh?
- I'm so frustrated.
- It's a magical room.
In any case, I think we need to
think about an explanation
for why that fuel container is here.
WHO LEFT THIS CONTAINER HERE AND WHY?
I'll place my vote at this point.
- On the most suspicious person right now?
- Yes.
Why do you keep looking at me?
Do you have a thing for me too?
- Jeez, you need a beating.
- He's gender-blind.
THE DETECTIVE CASTS 2 VOTES TOTAL,
1 OF WHICH IS CAST AFTER THE BRIEFING
- What's that?
- Okay, the first one.
TA-DA
- Wow.
- What's that?
That was really cool.
WHO WILL GET THE DETECTIVE'S FIRST VOTE?
All right.
At this moment,
the person I suspect
of being the culprit is...
- Really?
- Seriously?
PARK SHAMAN
- Really?
- Seriously?
- Park Shaman?
- That was unexpected.
Don't vote for me
because I have a tragic family history.
This is so infuriating.
She claims her younger brother is missing,
but this is someone who scraped together
500 million won to restore his sight.
If he really were missing,
she'd be out there
looking for him right now.
WHY IS SHE NOT LOOKING FOR HIM?
I felt her answer was a bit too vague,
so we need to uncover the truth.
There's so much more we need to find out.
The scene of the murder itself
is especially too complex.
Let's go find the truth.
- All right.
- Let's go catch the culprit!
- Let's go.
- Back at it again.
We have to get them!
THE SCENE OF THE CRIME
WILL REVEAL THE CULPRIT
Please check Mr. Village Head's room,
Detective.
- Got it.
- We didn't find much from there.
Okay, I will.
- Wait, everyone. Let's do this.
- Starting with Mr. Village Head?
Let's take turns
checking each other's cell phones.
- Look at this text here.
- Okay.
- It's from the youth association leader.
- Let me walk over this imaginary wall.
Kim Handsome.
- Can you see me?
- I can't.
- I didn't see the mannequin earlier.
- Wait, hang on.
What's this?
- Wait, what is that?
- It's not what I think it is, is it?
- It can't be.
- No way.
- Isn't this just a strap for the bed?
- Oh, is it?
But why is it sticking out like this?
- Just lift it up then.
- Oh gosh.
- Wow, you're so strong.
- Is that...
What is that?
- What's wrong?
- What is this?
What is it?
- Oh jeez.
- The ring!
- Take that out.
- Hurry, get it out.
Whose is this?
- I thought it was blood.
- Kim Handsome's!
Close that.
- You bastard.
- I said close that!
"Embalming a corpse"?
- Hang on.
- Is he actually crazy?
- This is just textbook--
- That nutjob.
Let's set it down.
- Don't come in here!
- We found the ring!
You got it all wrong.
"Wash and disinfect the entire body."
- It's not what you think.
-"Drain the blood while injecting..."
He was planning to do
something like taxidermy.
- A wax figure!
- Wax figure!
Did he plan to keep her here?
"Sew the mouth shut"?
It says to sew the mouth!
Was he trying to take her organs out?
- It says you have to empty the body.
- That sounds likely.
- Look at the blood. How awful is that?
- Oh, you scared me!
I read up on it, but I was too horrified
to go through with it.
So I gave it up.
- But you did go through with it!
- Then why did you keep all this?
To tell you the truth,
today's a special day for me and Je-in.
It's the five-year anniversary
of our Netflix-and-chill night.
Every year since then,
I come back to stay in this hotel
and visit the hospital too.
- Wait, you did the deed in the hospital?
- Of course.
Gross!
- He's insane.
- Anyway, I came here to see Je-in,
and I ran into her in the hotel lobby
even though we didn't arrange it.
- I was so happy that I hugged her.
- Please don't say more about that night.
- And I told her I'd missed her and all.
- She must've been terrified.
Then I slipped the ring on her finger.
Just like that?
When you haven't seen her for five years?
But I guess Je-in was surprised,
because she took the ring off,
tossed it, and told me off.
- Tell you off how?
- What did she say?
She said, "I'm so sick of this.
The nutjob is back."
- That's understandable.
- So I grabbed this and came up to my room.
Overwhelmed by my impulses,
I was wondering what to do next.
So your love was one-sided.
I was really hurt.
That Netflix-and-chill night
might not have happened.
But seriously, think about it.
Why would his eyes get so swollen?
- Look at that photo.
- July 31st...
- Look at his eyes.
- What happened to them?
Who is this?
- It's Handsome.
- Handsome.
- Oh jeez.
- Goodness gracious!
My Je-in has gotten pretty tall.
He's the worst.
- That lunatic.
- She was about 165 cm tall 5 years ago,
but she's around 175 cm now.
- How did that happen?
- Why is she so tall?
- We need to perform a rite for this.
- She grew so much.
Shoo!
Begone!
- The gods are angry too.
- It looks like he put makeup on himself.
- Tell me about it.
- I just drank wine with her.
- Look at the wine glasses.
- I see the wine.
- Only Mr. Handsome drank it.
- Je-in didn't drink any.
- She must've put something in the wine.
- She drugged him!
- So Director Jang did something to him.
- She did something to her inpatients.
Did she experiment on them?
- She did all that to drug you.
- That's right.
- That's nonsense.
- She tricked you.
- She fooled you. Wake up.
- An alcoholic would go nuts for drinks.
But first,
- how about you go in there too?
- Good idea.
- Or just lie down here.
- Yeah, you creep us out.
- Lie down with the mannequin.
- Here.
I'll put the roses here
so you can Netflix and chill now.
I'll just take a little break.
- Don't wander around.
- This is pretty tough.
Just stay with her.
- I had a look at Mr. Village Head's phone.
- Okay.
Look at this text.
It looks like the victim,
Jang Je-in, was out of the country.
- My Je-in?
- Oh jeez.
- No, just stay there.
- Stay there.
- My Je-in was abroad?
- Shoo, shoo! Begone, begone!
- I want to know too.
- Look.
Some reporter texted him and said,
"She's flying back to Korea
to hold a press conference."
"Do you know anything?"
Our Mr. Village Head would've met her
- and heard about it!
- He must've found out!
- That must be why he killed her!
- He must've heard!
Did you meet my Je-in?
- No.
- Did you meet my Je-in?
- He must have. For sure.
- When did you meet her?
- You have something. Grab him, Handsome!
- Hey, frisk him!
- Let's see your pocket.
- I only have my wallet here.
- Hand me that.
- I can't frisk him, so someone else do it.
How many pockets does this have?
One, two, three, four, jeez.
There are way too many pockets.
- I think there's something in here.
- Hey, watch where you're touching!
- The name on his ID is different.
- What?
PARK REAL SON
His name here
shouldn't be "Park Real Son."
- He's not Park Village Head.
- The photo!
- Let's see the photo.
- Did he assume a new identity?
- Wait, that's our village's--
- Wait, what?
His identity!
Who changes their identity like this?
- This is such a sloppy way to do it.
- Unbelievable.
- He's grabbing something!
- You just changed the photo!
- You'll anger the gods!
- Hang on.
I'll come clean.
I...
Subtitle translation by: Yenny Kang